This love in my heart,
it will burn on forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope that we'll never stop.
No matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting bones,
we'll reach it, we are home.
I'm
so truly grateful.
I ran into you on that day so long ago.
We laughed every moment
with tears in our eyes.
Till we knew we weren't alone.
The blowing wind came in
and joined us on our way.
And with it I know we'll rise.
We'll be flying up high.
Why, tell me why are you giving up?
Why, tell me why you want to fight alone?
Hey, what kind of future
do you think you have?
Your dream is already in your hands.
This love in my heart,
it will burn off forever!
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
I don't matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting
plans, we'll reach it.
We are home from the horizon
out on the edge of the world.
If there is a place that
I want to take you to?
Let's head for it then.
But as for the way we already know?
We promised it long ago.
You scream by your voice.
That can't break through the silence.
Feeling defeated?
It crushes your helpless heart.
I've got your back, I swear.
I'll always be here.
Let's put our fate within
this light under the sun.
Can you close your eyes and
just listen to my voice?
Let's find the answer together I'm
telling you in our path I trust that it
will lead us To another sea untarded
Cause now we are home On the horizon,
out on the edge of the world
There is a place that I want
to take you to Let's head for
it then But after the way,
we already know
We promised it long ago
Luffy's team had intended to use Peckham's
as a guide to Big Mom
on Whole Cake Island.
However, thanks to his
sudden disappearance,
they had little choice but to
follow Pudding's directions.
I'm worried about Peckham's.
We should look for him.
Frankly, I wouldn't even
know where to start.
He's a tough one.
He'll be fine.
You think so?
We just have to trust the map.
We won't have anything to be
afraid of if we aren't spotted,
so hopefully this path will work out.
Hey, where are we now?
We've barely left port.
Relax, we're still near Cacao Island.
Hey, I see an island.
All right!
I wonder what kind of snacks they'll have.
We know from the smell that it's
going to be something sweet.
According to the map, it's
probably going to be jam.
Really?
But we won't be stopping there.
Here, look.
Soon as we see jam island, then we turn.
We'll follow the directions
of Log Pose, too.
But it's jam, Nami!
Sweet, yummy jam!
A miracle island of jam, and
you're just going to ignore it?
Let's see.
To the right.
Okay.
Starboard, Luffy.
That's three o 'clock to the right.
Hear that?
Going right is the right way.
Going right to Sanji.
Free jam.
We'll have Sanji bake stuff for us.
Hard starboard.
Not that hard.
You're not very good at
this, are you, Luffy?
Like you could do any better.
My sweet jam.
According to Pudding,
If we turn towards the next island before
getting too close to
the one in front of us,
we can avoid the surveillance
network and sneak by.
I see.
So that's how you read the map.
Convenient.
Can you steer?
With pleasure.
Luffy, I'll take it from
here if you don't mind.
Okay.
In that case, I'll cook up
some dinner for us. Huh?
This is urgent.
I'll take care of it.
Please?
Luffy, wait a sec.
I'm in a hurry, though.
I gotta go cook. No!
I'm not gonna mess up this time.
That's right, you aren't.
Because I'm cooking no
more kitchen for you.
All right, but I'm not paying.
I don't want money! What?
Let me try, Pedro. Switch out.
I want to help the team, too.
All right.
Let's see.
Hey!
The water's grape-colored!
It is! Wow!
There is an island that
spills juice around here.
It's no harm to us.
What?
Does that mean we can drink the ocean?
This place is paradise!
Pedro, you know a lot about
this place. Why is that?
I've been here once before.
Huh? Ah!
A giant sea centipede they
reside in the waters around here
Taste my blade.
Come, insect.
Meanwhile, on Hallscake Island...
Crocambush!
Sir! Mama! Please!
Mama!
You can't do this!
Crocambush!
Mama's condition is acting up again!
We must take action. Tout suite.
What is our request, c 'est Giri?
A cheeky one.
Cro-cambouche.
Where the heck would we even start?
Is that the one with all the
cream puffs piled up, isn't it?
Beaucoup complique.
Oh, well, actually, I may
have just la solution.
Wasn't there a tourist group of cream
puffs staying at a hotel nearby?
I'm afraid they checked out this morning.
Do we have to make one, then?
Call the chef!
I would like to do something
special with the dough.
Get me some almonds.
My chef contacts the Minister of Nuts.
Mama is currently en route to Sweet City.
She's coming here to the capital?
What if she destroys her Shit Royale?
We can't talk her out of it.
It seems she's completely lost her senses.
The death toll is still rising.
Issue an evacuation order, immediately.
Only a croquembush can stop Mama's
rampage now. This way! Quickly now!
Evacuate the city!
Mama, please stop!
Mama, can you not please?
Bring me my croquembush, you fool!
Sweet City's under attack!
Mama's headed towards downtown!
Well, what now?
Mama's hunger pains are always
bad, but this is catastrophic.
They always just pop up out
of the blue. You're right.
Until she gets a bite of whatever
she craves, she will not stop.
And can't be stopped!
Just evacuate the residence!
It's all we can do! Hurry!
She's coming!
Mama's having one of
her tantrums! Why now?
This is her city!
Mama, stop it!
This is not the place!
You'll wreck your own castle!
No use.
She can't hear us.
I want cro-ke-boosh!
Cro-ke-boosh, right now!
Oh, come on!
Run!
This isn't the flavor!
Useless!
All of you!
Bring it to me!
Thank you!
It's Governor Moscato!
The minister of gelato and 16th
son of the Charlotte family.
If he's one of Mama's children,
then I'm sure he can do something.
Help, Mrs.
Moscato speaking.
Come in.
What's our status and where
is that croquembouche?
Regretablement, le chasset will be at
least another half hour before he's done.
It'll be far too late by then.
We can't allow her to destroy the castle.
Mama!
You must stop this!
Who's there?
Mama, it's Moscato!
Don't you recognize me?
Where is my croquembush, boy?
because all I want is croquemotia.
Mama, the chefs are making
it as fast as they can.
Please just give us 30 minutes
and we'll have it ready.
You have my word.
Forget it, brother.
Run away, Moss.
There's no stopping her.
And let her destroy the whole capital?
Are you crazy?
Out of my way. No!
Don't you recognize your own son?
Mama!
Is it life or treat?
Oh, no, anything but life or treat.
She's going to steal his lifespan away.
He's your own son! Stay calm!
You'll get your dessert soon enough!
Mama!
Have mercy! Ma!
Why don't you have some
whipped cream while you wait?
An appetizer?
Doesn't that sound tasty?
The treat is just not ready. I'm sorry.
Oh, you're gonna be sorry.
I said life or treat!
Oh please no keep your cool moss
If you show fear then your lifespan
will be taken away from you
Please don't do this mama I won't
stop here anymore I promise I beg you,
spare my money!
Forty years!
No, big brother!
Governor Piscato!
She murdered her own son?
This is a nightmare!
Run for your lives!
No one can stop her now!
What a tragic state of affairs.
Somebody's coming down
the river of juice is that
it can't be but it is
everyone out of the way.
Whoa, it's Jinbei!
Someone help me.
We're gonna get gobbled up.
And look, here's a crooked bush.
He must have caught those tourist
green puffs when they left the hotel.
Look at that beautiful blaze.
The minister of candy's work, no doubt.
Over here. Huh?
Don't you dare get in
my way Open wide, round!
Now that is yummy!
We did it!
Mama's rampage has ended at last! Mmm!
That really hit the spot!
If I'm delicious, then I can die happy!
Thank you, boss.
You saved us.
I'll give the chefs a call.
The crisis is over.
We must summon all the ministers.
Rest our lack of a daily
time for the big tea party!
Hmm.
Kimbei, what a pleasure it is to see
my loyal Knight of the Sea here today.
That reminds me, I never thanked you
properly for bringing me that poneglyph.
Only wish I could read it.
Ma-ma-ma-ma-ma.
What brings you here today?
Is there something you need?
Oh, it seems there's been some
remodeling done here in the city
Might this be your work?
No, ma 'am I arrived here just a moment
ago I haven't a clue what happened
Oh?
If you can spare but
a moment of your time?
There are some things I would
like to speak to you about today.
It's important.
You're not going to
leave my crew, are you?
I have faith in Straw Hat,
and I am confident that he
will change this world someday.
He is young, I know,
but I do not believe that
any of the four emperors
have what it takes to
become king of these seas.
But Straw Hat Luffy isn't like them.
That boy is something special.
Therefore, I've decided that I
want to lend him my strength.
I'm so...
I'm so weak!
More than that, I want to join his crew.
I want to ride upon his ship, and I
want to dedicate my life to his journey.
In the end,
I believe the world he creates will be a
world where fishmen are truly free at last.
We all know plenty about Luffy,
Jinbei, if we're being frank.
You've been going on and on
about him for the past two years.
I don't disagree with
your decision, though.
If you want to join Luffy that
much, then maybe you should.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Did I talk about him that much?
Just go, Jean-Babe.
We don't mind.
Are you certain?
We can't even complain, Captain.
We totally get how you feel.
And besides, you quit your job
in the Neptune Army to help us.
That's why you're a pirate, right?
We were just a bunch of
slaves from Marie Joie,
but you were willing to do
anything to fight by our side.
Even when you joined the Warlords,
you only did it to advance the
status of us fishmen, right?
Same with big mom.
That's why you got all buddy-buddy with
her to protect the Ryugu kingdom You throw
the name of an emperor around and even the
real tough guys will get off your back!
Everything you've done
has been to help our
people you turned our whole lives around.
You've done enough for us.
It's all right
Yeah, Captain now is your
time break out and be free
That's what you gotta do!
We'll be fine without you.
Don't underestimate us.
Time to start living for yourself.
Going where you want.
Thank you.
But I don't know.
Even if we're cool with
the captain leaving,
I have a feeling Big Mom ain't
gonna be too happy about this.
If she gets mad, then all
he can do is run away.
Maybe better to swim.
Huh?
But then what's Aladdin supposed to do?
He's a member of Big Mom's family
since he's married to Lady Prawlane.
Now, what was that?
You aren't worried about
little old me, are you?
Ah, it's her!
Sha, sha, sha.
Were you naughty boys talking
about me behind my back? Oh, crap.
Did she hear us?
You're hiding something from
me, my darling little hubby.
Aladdin, fuss up.
If Mama got angry at your crew,
were you gonna scurry off
in the middle of the night?
and leave me behind?
No, uh, I would ask you first, my dear.
What makes you think you need to ask?
I choose you over Mama
any day of the week.
If you have to leave,
then take me with you.
Oh, so passionate!
Forgive me, Waratsumi.
I just brought you here,
and I'm already leaving.
Aw, it's fine.
I love being with these
guys, so I'm still happy.
Well, what say you, Praline?
Will Mama forgive me?
Or rather, will she forgive
us if I try to leave?
Good question.
Others have tried it before.
I don't know exactly how the negotiations
went, but I know that they're dead.
Oh, Commander Mascotto!
He just wanted to protect
us and now he's dead!
No, this can't be true!
You've got to get off, Mascotto!
Please don't die!
We've finally decided to show up.
Hurry and take him away. Yes, ma 'am.
Out of the way.
Listen up, damn it.
Every single second.
You understand me?
Hell if I know!
But if you cross mama, this is what's gonna
happen to you even if you're her child.
Hmm, so you really want
to leave me, Jinbae?
Don't go, boss!
Why would you leave?
Don't you love us anymore? Shut up!
Don't ask someone why they're leaving.
Do you know how pathetic that sounds?
What does it matter, anyway?
Jinbei is a pirate, and we
always live the way we choose.
That said, having a
pledge of loyalty reneged
brings shame to a leader.
Jinbei, I'm losing a very
powerful asset here. Namely, you.
Well, perhaps...
Perhaps, you say?
If I'm losing something, you should, too.
That means you have to pay the price.
Ma-ma-ma-ma-ma!
Bring me the roulette!
What?!
Now spin it!
Come on, let's see what
you lose, shall we?
I can't wait!
Meanwhile, Luffy and company continue
their trek to Whole Cake Island.
Yummy!
I'm afraid we're not making
much progress, are we?
No kidding.
You want to start a
campfire and take a nap?
And get attacked by those ants again?
No thank you.
At night time, the syrupy
seas get cold and solidify.
When the sun rises, it'll
begin to flow again.
Tell us these things beforehand next time.
Just melt this batch of starch syrup, and
hopefully we'll be on our way in no time.
You got it.
Keep going.
We're not exactly safe here.
I only put those sea ants to sleep.
They're gonna be mad when they wake up.
Oh, undoubtedly so.
Those ants can eat an entire ship.
I'd know since it happened to mine.
No way! Hey, Pedro!
You said you came here
once before, but why?
Pedro and Peckhams?
They used to be pirates
and traveled here together.
Really?
You should have told me!
I was so naive.
I thought of myself as a grand explorer,
but I soon became a wanted man.
At any rate, I only accompanied
Peckhams half the way.
Please keep this story between us.
I wanted to help Master Catviper.
So I was scouring these
waters for poneglyphs.
But when I trespassed in Big Mom's
territory it became my last voyage.
I faced a devastating defeat here.
I don't talk about this often.
Pedro I never knew.
You have bad memories
but you still came back.
If my experience helps then it will all
be worth it if you Karoo can rescue Sanji.
Besides this might be a chance to
rectify my failure from last time.
I heard that Yugara
went to the whale tree.
And that our kings showed
Yugara the road poneglyph there.
That was quite a surprise.
I'll put it this way.
No one outside the Kozuki
clan has seen that place.
In nearly 26 years or so.
Specifically since they showed
it to Goldie Roger and his crew.
The king of the pirates was there?
Yes And after that, he sailed to
Laugh Tale and earned that title.
In other words,
Duke Dogstorm and Master
Catviper think Yugara
have the same qualities
that Roger possessed.
They showed Yugara the
Road Poneglyph because
they believed you might need it someday.
What is your plan after
Yugara defeat Kaido?
That's too far ahead.
I haven't even thought about it.
If you, Karoo, want to see this through,
you'll need Big Mom's Road Poneglyph.
Since we're this far into her territory,
it might be your best, if not
only, opportunity to find it.
So in addition to taking back Sanji,
I believe we should steal Big
Mom's Road Poneglyph as well.
But can we do that?
But rescuing Sanji might
be hard enough already.
Robin did ask me about
it, but I don't know.
Maybe after we save Sanji? I understand.
I'll get the Poneglyph,
you, Karoo, get Sanji.
That satisfactory?
When we reach the island, can
you, Karoo, buy me a little time?
I swear I won't fail again. Hold on.
We'll help you.
I mean, you're doing
this for us, after all.
I'm fine.
It'll be hard enough to keep Sanji safe.
Rescuing him is just the beginning.
I get it.
Well, good luck.
Good. It's settled.
Shouldn't we talk this through?
Sometimes I wonder,
do things work out for Luffy because
he was born under a lucky star?
What was that, Brooke?
Nothing.
I'm lucky myself.
What are you talking about?
Don't be weird.
Ah!
The ants woke up! No!
Protect the Snow!
Hey, you guys!
Wake up!
Yoho?
What is it?
Look!
So we finally made it!
Oh ho ho ho!
That's one fancy looking island!
So this is the kind of
place an emperor lives!
That's a big cake!
The tallest cake there
is actually a castle.
Naturally, that's where
Big Mom lives. Oh, wow!
Nami, should I keep steering
us straight? Uh-huh.
We're headed to that cape.
It's a hole in the security net.
I see.
Everything's gone just like Pudding said.
Yeah.
I wish there was some way to
thank her for all her help.
If we hadn't met her, I don't know
if we would have made it this far.
That is so true.
Look!
Somebody's on the shore!
No way!
It's Sanji!
Hey!
Sanji!